2030 and
I want
to show
you the
day in
the life
of a
person in
2030 you
might
not have
noticed this
but I
was gently
woken up
with this
device this
is
actually a
fitness tracker
but as
you
can see
it looks
like a
luxury product
not just
that this
bed is
actually smart
this side
of the
bed is
warm because
I
like warm
this side
of the
bed is
cold
and it
' s
all controlled
by that
device
there in
fact that
device has
Ai and
it
makes sure
to put
me in
the right
temperature at
time in
the
night not
just that
all my
stats appear
here
all right
welcome to
my bathroom
and as
you can
see I
have a
nice little
smart
mirror where
all my
stacks from
last
night are
printed on
the mirror
it '
s all
fed in
from this
in real
time and
one
more cool
thing you
probably notice
is
that there
are no
brushes or
toothpaste
we all
just goggle
with this
nice little
liquid and
spit it
out we
only use
brushes or
floss when
something gets